(Amy:)Well, I'm not sure
how this is scored,
(Sheldon:)but I believe
we may have won.
(Leonard:)Sheldon?
(Howard:)Where did he go?
(Howard:)We're looking for Sheldon,
not Marmaduke.
(Sheldon:)You whistled?
(Leonard:)What is that?
Raiders of the Lost Ark
(Sheldon:)with 21 additional seconds.
(Sheldon:)If I can't see it,
no one else can see it.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, this is crazy.
(Sheldon:)No. Crazy was leaving
the projection booth unattended.
(Sheldon:)Listen to me.
(Leonard:)You are over-tired.
You're not thinking right.
(Leonard:)Put the movie back
before we get into trouble.
(Sheldon:)Trouble is my middle name,
Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Actually, it's Lee,
but I prefer Trouble.
(Wil Wheaton:)Oh, look who
they let in.
(Sheldon:)Don't worry, Wil Wheaton.
I was just leaving.